人人影視
YYeTs.com
本字幕由人人影視字幕組翻譯
禁止用作任何商業盈利行為
翻譯： 暴龍蛋      阿髻      Kiko
翻譯： DustD         胖兔純
時間軸： 濃子   萌    校對： 胖兔純
后期： 孤帆    總監： 米小勒   胖兔純
塞勒姆
第一季  第七集
《塞勒姆》前情提要
Previously on "Salem"...
"偉大的儀式"
Ritum magni.
大祭典
The grand rite?
這里提到了這個物件 "惡靈"
It says this object, this "Malum,"
在歷史上
is thought to be present
每次大祭典中都會出現
at every grand rite throughout history.
這是邪惡之物
This object is evil.
它將使大地生靈涂炭  以迎惡魔回歸
It consecrates the earth for the devil's return.
這是一個包裹  那一定有收件人
It was here for delivery. Someone was expecting it.
就是說其他人都已背叛我了
So the others have turned on me.
沒錯
Yes.
每個人
Each and every one.
蘿絲
Rose?
每個人
Everyone.
如果你希望約翰·奧登活著
If you wish for John Alden to live,
你就必須完成大祭典
you will complete the grand rite.
什么是大祭典
What is the grand rite?
你們以為可以把我像垂線木偶一樣任意擺布嗎
You think you can dangle me like a puppet?
你們才是木偶  你們所有人  木偶
You're the puppets, all of you -- puppets!
我記得你說過
I thought you said
土星會迫使她說出真相
Saturn would compel her to speak the truth.
沒錯
It did.
有時候  真相就是一個謎語
Sometimes the truth is a riddle.
那謎底呢
And the answer?
我得好好思索一番
I must think and then think again.
父親
Father?
來吧  孩子
Come, child.
是時候來談談你父親的事了
It's time we talked about your father.
你未經我同意把惡靈帶到了塞勒姆
You brought the malum to Salem behind my back.
他們將無一幸免
Not one of them will survive.
照這樣下去  我們也是一樣
Nor the rest of us, at this rate.
我們已被困十天
10 days becalmed.
水和食物快消耗光了
Nearly out of food and water.
除非借助東風
We've no hope
否則我們毫無希望
unless we catch the wind.
我們要借助的不是東風  船長
It is not the wind that we must catch, captain.
是巫師
It is a witch.
看著我  小姑娘
Girl, look at me.
我們已經調查過所有你認為是巫師的
We have searched every passenger and crew member
乘客和船員
for your supposed witches.
毫無發現
None were found.
船上有個巫師
There is a witch on this ship.
你能懂我意思嗎  船長
You understand me, captain?
為了阻止我  他將殺光所有船上的人員
The witch will kill everyone aboard in order to stop me.
我們會找出這個巫師的
We will find the witch.
別出錯
Make no mistake.
否則下一個就是你
It could just as well be your head.
蘿絲未經我同意把惡靈帶到了這兒
Rose brought the malum here behind my back
想要背著我完成大祭典
to complete the grand rite without me.
是誰的提議讓清教徒的矛頭
Whose idea was it to turn the puritans' hatred
對準他們自己
against themselves?
利用他們來完成
To use them to achieve
諸世紀以來的第一場大祭典
the first grand rite in centuries?
是誰讓大祭典得以實現
Who made that possible?
是我
Me.
而你和那個賤人卻不相信我
Yet you and that foul bitch mistrusted me.
你罪加一等  因為你低估了我
And much worse for you, you underestimated me.
但殺了死亡之神
But killing the Samhain,
你知道這樣做有多嚴重嗎
do you have any idea what you've done?
問題不是
The question
我有沒有意識到它的嚴重性
is not whether I understand what I have done,
而是你有沒有意識到你現在該干什么
but whether you understand what you must now do.
我明白了
I do.
你擁有了古老的權利
You have claimed the ancient right.
我奉你為新任的死亡之神
I recognize you as the new Samhain.
我愿意臣服于你的力量  為你浴血奮戰
I will honor and obey your power, earned in blood,
我會傳話給其他人的
and share the word with the rest of the hive.
狩獵滿月即將來臨
Full hunter's moon is soon upon us.
屆時我們還需要八名死者
We need eight more dead by then.
我有個計劃...
And I have a plan...
只需一著  就能讓我們離目標咫尺之遙
to put us within reach of our goal with one single move.
一次獲得三個祭品
Three sacrificed all at once.
但你給我聽清楚了
But mark me well --
如果任何人敢違背我的意愿  我唯你是問
If anyone goes behind my back, I hold you responsible.
你會付出代價的
You will pay for it,
不然就是你的妻子和女兒
or your wife and sweet daughter will.
*擂我戰鼓*
*Pound me the witch drums*
*鼓鳴震天*
*Witch drums*
*擂我戰鼓*
*Pound me the witch drums*
*鼓鳴震天*
*The witch drums*
*寧入地獄*
*Better pray for hell*
*不留人間*
*Not hallelujah*
間諜
A spy?
什么意思
What do you mean?
他在為法國人賣命嗎
Is he working for the French?
不
No!
當然不是
Of course not.
我不應該告訴你的
I should have said nothing.
但你的疑心遲早會致我們于死地
But your infernal snooping only endangers us all.
你父親是個秘密間諜
Your father is a confidential agent.
他只是偶爾會為一個
He makes very occasional reports
外國勢力機構提供一些情報
to agents representing another foreign power.
是誰  他為什么要這樣做
Then who? And why?
是誰重要嗎
What does it matter to whom your father speaks?
都是政治而已  親愛的
It's just politics, dear.
沒什么大不了的
Of no import.
沒什么大不了
No import?
你是說我父親是個叛國賊這沒什么大不了的嗎
That my father is a traitor is of no import?!
不許你這么說
Never say that.
你父親不是叛國賊
Your father is not a traitor.
他是一個有著崇高理想的人
He is a man of the highest ideals!
他所做的一切都是為了你
Everything your father he does, he does for you.
為了你好  你少插手他的事情
Keep out of his affairs for your own good.
你少糊弄我了  母親
I am utterly unconvinced by your story, mother.
他就這么突然消失在我眼前
He seemed to vanish before my eyes.
我不會道歉的
I make no apologies.
我絕不會無視眼前所發生的一切
And I choose to walk through life with my eyes open.
就像你一樣
Unlike you.
我知道你覺得我是個完全沒主見的蠢女人
I know you think me a stupid woman with no curiosity,
但你不明白
but you don't understand.
問題是一旦你知道真相
The problem with knowing things
你就再也無法視而不見
is that you can never unknow them.
來了嗎
Has it arrived?
耐心點
Patience.
這就是...
This...
我期待已久的船上傳來的信息
...message I've been waiting for from the ship.
無風
Windstille.
"我們被困了
"We are becalmed.
他調查了一番  但沒有結果"
He searches, but I remain hidden."
如果他們沒能看住他
If they fail to hold him,
他可能隨時會來
he could arrive at any time.
你警告了瑪麗·西布里了嗎
Have you warned Mary Sibley?
沒
No.
她對德國人的事一無所知
She knows nothing of the Germans
她也不知道我和他們有聯系
nor of my contact with them
更無法預料即將到來的威脅
nor of the impending threat.
如果他們真有能力牽制住他
If they succeed in keeping him at bay,
她也就沒必要知道了
then she has no need to know.
如果他勢不可擋
And if he cannot be stopped,
游戲就又有得玩了  不是嗎
well, then it's an entirely new game, isn't it?
這可能帶來很多威脅  你不該告訴她嗎
It threatens everything. Shouldn't you tell her?
情報就是力量
Knowledge is power.
說到力量
And with regard to power,
如今她的力量已經足夠之多
she has more than her share at the moment,
你說是嗎
wouldn't you agree?
你確定這么做是正確的嗎
Are you sure you've done the right thing?
當你拉我入伙的時候  你確定嗎
Were you sure when you brought me in?
我確定
Yes.
我救了你的命
I saved your life.
我會一直保你平安
And I will never cease saving it.
我知道
I know.
過來
Come.
我必須找到惡靈
I must find the Malum.
就在約翰·奧登手上
John Alden has it.
是的
Yes.
他也知道自己手握權柄
And he knows he has something of power,
巫師們不惜性命也要奪回手中
something witches would kill and die for.
他一定會將它藏在隱匿之處
He will have well-hidden it.
那你要怎么找
Well, then how will you find it?
我打算搜尋他的意識
I've a mind to search his mind.
夢游術嗎  不行
Dream walking? No.
一定還有別的辦法
There has to be another way.
時間不多了  緹圖芭
We're running out of time, Tituba.
沒有惡靈和它帶來的一切
Without the Malum and all it contains,
大祭典便無法完成
our grand rite is not possible.
相信我
Trust me.
進去之后我會立刻找到惡靈
Once inside, I'll find the Malum,
隨即離開
and then I'll get out.
進去
Inside?
你要進入不是房屋而是人心
It is not a house you invade but a man!
這個人還很特別
And not just any man.
你確定是為尋找惡靈  而不是只想接近他嗎
Are you sure it is the Malum you seek and not just access to him?
不管我對約翰有何私情
Whatever my personal feelings are for John,
我只是為了找到惡靈
I am only seeking the Malum.
你可曾想過
Do you have any idea
闖入他的夢境之中
what crawling around inside his dreams
對你們倆有何影響
could do to you and to him?
這可能會損毀你們兩人的心智
It could leave either or both of you shattered,
無法分辨現實與夢境
unable to tell dreams from reality.
你可能會迷失或者被困在夢里
You could be lost, trapped!
還有別的辦法能找到惡靈
There are other ways to find the Malum.
說實話  我很害怕
I cannot lie. I am afraid.
很好
Good.
怕是好事
Be afraid.
照看著我
Watch over me.
但這是我的選擇
But this is my choice.
不管你是否幫忙  我意已決
I will do this with or without you.
緹圖芭  現在就送我過去
Tituba, send me. Now.
約翰·鄧恩的詩《歌》
流星隕落  奔走采擷
Go now. Catch a falling star.
首烏似女  珠胎暗結
Get with child a mandrake root.
時光逝去  穿梭而至
Travel back where past years are.
惡魔足印  因循踏遍
Through the cloven devil's hoof.
汝之所求  皆在其心
What you seek is in his heart.
天使之術  現其所思
Know his thoughts through angel's art.
巫焰燎燎  萬事皆備
As torches ever ready be,
穿越白晝之門  一  二  三
through daylight's gate step one, two, three.
你為什么等了這么久
Why have you waited so long?
玩得開心嗎
Enjoying yourself?
我還沒找到
I didn't find it yet.
但我知道我能
But I know I can.
這片海有問題
This sea is unnatural.
我能聞到  感覺到
I smell it. I feel it.
我們被籠罩在黑暗的術法之中
We are under a dark enchantment.
我們把船搜了個遍
We have searched high and low.
船上沒有巫師
There is no witch on this ship!
我說絕對有
And I say there is.
每個人都盤查過了
We have searched everyone.
查了兩遍  巫師到底在哪里
Twice. So where is the witch?
就在這里
Right here.
繩結在哪里  船長
Where is the knot, captain?
你的繩結藏在哪里
Where have you hidden the knot?
那綁住了海風的繩結在哪里
Where is the knot that binds the wind?
去死吧[德語]
Friss scheibe und stirb!
你不會活著到達新世界的[德語]
Sie werden die neue welt nie lebend erreichen!
我的脖子
My neck!
掛在我脖子上
Around my neck!
再見了[德語]
Auf wiedersehen.
船長  起風了
Captain, the wind's up.
船帆已經鼓滿
The sails are full.
現在這條船歸我管
I am now master of this ship.
告訴舵手  向西航行
Tell the helmsman due west.
閉上眼睛
Close your eyes...
打破一枚雞蛋
and you break an egg.
然后想象自己的婚禮
And you imagine your wedding,
你站在教堂前面
so you're standing there in front of the meeting house
手捧鮮花
holding a bunch of flowers.
喜鐘為你敲響
The bells are ringing for you.
等你睜開雙眼
And then when you open your eyes,
就能看見未來丈夫的臉
you see the face of the man you're to marry.
但我們已經知道多莉會嫁給誰了
But we already know who Dollie'll marry.
糟老頭喬·巴克
Stinky, old Joe Barker.
我才不會
I will not.
但你已經和他行連理之禮了
But -- but you've already bundled with him.
還沒有
Have not.
馬上就要了
But you're going to.
是的
Yes.
就在今晚
Tonight.
一定還有其他人更適合我
There's got to be someone else for me.
如果有
Well, if there is,
金星之鏡會展示給你
The venus glass will show him to you.
但你得先把茶給喝了
But first you have to drink the tea.
全喝光
All of it.
你看到了嗎
Did you see that?
你看到什么了
What did you see?
你看到喬·巴克了嗎
Did you see joe barker?
沒有  我...
No, I...
我不確定看到了什么  但...
I don't know what I saw, but...
我...
I...
我必須得走了
But I -- but I have to go now.
我快趕不上連理儀式了
Um, I'll -- I'll be late for my bundling,
如果破壞了這樁天賜良緣
And my mother will beat me
母親會打死我的
for ruining a perfectly fine match.
我們都該走了
We all should go, too.
我做到了
I did it.
效果就像
And it worked just --
就像你描述的那樣
just like you said it would.
我先給她下藥
I-I gave her the potion first,
然后我在腦海中想象
and then I pictured it in my mind,
她就看到了
and she saw it.
這還只是開始
And this is just the beginning.
下一步你要助我將塞勒姆逼入絕境
Next you will help push Salem over the edge,
但首先
But first...
你得學會如何讓靈魂脫離軀體
You must learn to walk wherever you will
任意游走
without your body.
主啊我祈求一睹你真容
I begged to see your face, lord.
難道我面前的就是嗎
Am I looking at it now?
人們都說發瘋的第一個征兆
They say it's the first sign of folly,
就是自言自語
talking to oneself.
我沒有自言自語
I wasn't talking to myself.
我是對主祈禱
But to god.
或是我父親
Or my father.
如果這兩者有區別的話
If there is a difference.
你父親在這兒嗎
Is he here?
更糟
Worse.
在這兒
Here.
看來我們并沒有想象中那么不同
I think we're not so different.
如果不是已經有了這么多煩心事
That would worry me immensely
聽到你這么說還真是讓我擔憂
were I not already consumed with other worries.
顯然有些真相不能在書里找到
And apparently there are some truths not contained in books.
實踐
Knowledge
才能出真知
must be tested against the anvil of experience.
而我一直以為的真知卻在昨晚被徹底顛覆
Last night my knowledge cracked like poorly forged steel.
聽到那個巫婆說的話之后
After what that witch said,
我開始懷疑一切
I can be sure of nothing but my doubts.
對所有事物
I doubt everything.
我的書本  工具  方法
My books, my tools, my methods.
甚至我自己
Even myself.
那你就用自己所擁有的武器來戰斗
Then you fight with the weapons you have.
你是指
Meaning?
如果你滿腹疑云
If all you have is doubt,
就讓懷疑成為你的武器
then you make doubt itself the weapon.
你質疑一切
You question everything.
甚至我自己
Even myself.
尤其是你自己
Especially yourself.
我相信主把我倆聚在一起是有理由的
I do believe god brought us together for a reason.
為了把對方逼瘋嗎
To drive each other insane?
不
No.
因為彌漫在塞勒姆的陰霾需要的光明之多
'cause the shadow over Salem requires more light
我們單獨一人都無法提供
than either of us can provide alone.
你比任何人都更了解
You know more than anyone about...
了解一切
Well, everything.
你對夢境知道多少
So what do you know about dreams?
未被發現的國度
The undiscovered country.
什么
What?
夢境
Dreams.
多數人無視它
Most men dismiss them.
但根據我的計算
But by my calculation,
一個活滿圣經全壽命70年的人
a man who lives his full biblical span of 70 years
會花其中的20年活在另一個夢境國度
will spend as many as 20 of them in another realm,
在那里一切都是幻境
where nothing is as it seems.
你認為夢境是真的
So you believe they're real?
沒錯
They are.
我們自己的新大陸
Our own private America,
一個充滿恐懼和愉悅的新世界
A new world filled with equal parts terror and delight.
顯然人不需要進鬼屋也能見著鬼
Apparently one not need be a house to be haunted.
你的意思是
What do you mean?
你不是唯一一個擁有無數欲望
You're not the only one who knows what it feels like
卻只能在夢中成真的人
to hold desires that come true only in dreams.
每天早晨  我們都面臨抉擇
But every morning, we have a choice.
忘記夢境
Forget our dreams...
或者活在夢想中
or live them.
當我還是小姑娘的時候
My mother sewed Mr. Barker and me
我母親把巴克先生和我縫進這個袋里
into this bag when I was a girl.
我們談天說地  度過了愉快的夜晚
Such pleasant nights we spent talking of this and that.
這些縫線防止你們在婚禮當晚之前
That stitch keeps you from having too much pleasure
過度享樂
before the wedding night.
腰部以下安分點
Nothing below the waist.
你真的去過七角閣樓嗎
Is it true you've been in the house of seven gables?
是的  我常去那
Oh, yes. Many times.
我朋友梅西如今就住在那兒
My friend Mercy lives there now.
你靠近她難道不會害怕嗎
Aren't you afraid to be close to her?
不會
No.
那你害怕靠近我嗎
Are you afraid to be close to me?
死丫頭
Wicked girl!
這個睡袋見證了三代婚姻
That bag's seen three generations married!
這事沒完  小丫頭
This isn't over, little missy!
我會去告訴你母親的
I'll take this up with your mother!
它在哪兒  親愛的
Where is it, my love?
告訴我它在哪兒
Show me where it is.
我  我不明白
I-I don't understand.
-不明白嗎  -不明白
- No? - No.
如今這一切說明什么
What does this mean?
你在乎嗎
Do you care?
這是真的
It is,
我們在一起
we are.
你只要知道這個就夠了
That's all that matters.
這樣足夠真實了嗎
Real enough for you?
還是這樣
Or this?
我得知道它在哪兒
I need to know where it is.
什么
What?
吉爾斯·科里
我找到惡靈了
I found the Malum.
就在科里的墳墓里
It's in Corey's grave.
奧登把它藏在了科里的墳墓里
Alden has hidden it in Corey's grave.
我警告過你的
I warned you.
進入任何人的夢境都十分危險
Dream walking in any man is dangerous,
更別說是你愛的人了
let alone one that you love.
你可能會徹底地迷失其中再也出不來了
You could lose your way and never come back.
別再進入那人的夢境了
Keep out of that man's head.
那小婊子撕爛了我曾祖母的連理睡袋
Little bitch tore my great-gran's bundling bag.
你那個有口臭的兒子
And your stink-breathed boy
在你的寶貝睡袋上戳了個洞
poked a hole in your precious bag,
還想在我女兒身上戳一個
tried to poke one in my girl!
那個睡袋上
There's no holes in that bag
只有她逃走時撕開的洞
but the ones she tore running out.
誰會相信你們巴克家說的話
And who'd believe you or any Barker?
看見沒  親愛的  起作用了
See, my dear? It's working.
誰都知道你們是一伙騙子
Everyone knows you're a pack of liars
靠著欺騙我們大家才發家致富
and cheats getting rich off the rest of us.
你要是不停止侮辱我們家族
You stop talking filth about my family
我就讓你不能再說話
or I'll stop you talking.
笑什么笑  小賤人
What are you laughing at, you little minx?!
巴克一族就算是烏合之眾
Those Barkers may be a foul lot,
但是他們富得流油
but they have money enough,
配你這樣的貨色已經是綽綽有余了
and it was a fine match for the likes of you,
都是你犯蠢毀了這門好親事
and you had to ruin it with your silly ideas.
奧登上尉
Captain Alden,
你這么匆忙是要去哪里
where are you off to with such urgency?
不去哪里
Nowhere.
就是  去呼吸一下新鮮空氣
Just...taking in the air.
我完全理解
Oh, I understand completely.
你可能早已不習慣鄉鎮生活
You're not a man used to town life.
你的身體渴望著那種無拘無束的狂野
Your body probably longs for the wilderness.
上尉
Captain?
抱歉  我
I'm sorry. I...
我不知道自己突然怎么了
I don't know what overcame me.
請原諒我
Please excuse me.
奧登上尉  無上榮幸
Captain Alden. An honor --
見到你很高興
and I hope a pleasure to see you.
你中意哪個呢
Anyone take your fancy?
是  我至少需要三個
Yes. I need at least three.
聰明女孩
Clever girl.
拜你讓多莉看到的東西所賜
Thanks to what you made Dollie see,
鎮里的人已經多半認為
the town is more than halfway to seeing
巴克一家是巫師了
the Barkers as witches.
如今只需一點火花來引燃大火
Now one spark will light the fire.
記得我曾告訴過你的話嗎
You remember all I told you?
是的
Yes.
但那真的有用嗎
But will it really work?
我怎樣才能離開我的身體
How will I leave my body?
想象你的極樂世界
Follow your bliss.
它會引領你脫離肉體
It will lead you out of your body
飛出窗外
and out of the window.
保持專注  并且記住
Stay focused and remember,
你今晚的任務是嚇壞杜克太太
your job tonight is to terrify Mrs. Trask.
讓她看到巴克太太
Make her see Mrs. Barker.
必須要讓她四處宣揚自己被巴克太太攻擊
She must tell everyone she was attacked by Mrs. Barker.
我明白
I understand.
你現在就要送我去了嗎
Are you gonna send me now?
閉上你的眼睛
Close your eyes.
想象你要去的地方
Picture where you want to go.
多莉
Dollie?
該死  如果你不管管你那該死的貓
Damn. If you don't learn to control your damn cat,
我就親手把它皮剝了
I'll skin it myself.
這不過是一場夢
This is but a dream.
生命本身也許就是一場夢
Life itself might be but a dream.
為何不及時行樂呢
Why not enjoy it?
別亂動  奧登上尉
Try to remain still, Captain Alden.
你在這做什么
What are you doing here?
學習上帝造物的神奇
Learning the wonders of god's own creation.
約翰
John?
你在哪  約翰
Where are you, John?
瑪麗
Mary!
瑪麗  快出來
Mary, come out now!
瑪麗
Mary!
瑪麗  瑪麗
Mary! Mary!
瑪麗  快出來
Mary, come out now!
瑪麗  瑪麗  快出來
Mary! Mary, come out now!
-瑪麗  -緹圖芭
- Oh, Mary. - Oh, Tituba.
沒事了
It's okay.
你回家了
You're home.
你為什么還要回去
Why did you go back?
我跟你說了別回去
I told you not to go back.
你還讓這個第一次的自己到處走
And you left this one to walk alone on her first time.
任何事都可能發生
Anything could have happened.
我知道  我很抱歉
I know. I'm sorry.
我只是想再見他一面
I just wanted to see him again.
我失去控制了
I lost control.
你穿上衣服
You get your clothes on.
你得來幫我忙
You're coming to help me.
不不  你要去哪
No, no. Where are you going?
去給你摘個蘋果
Shh. To fetch you an apple
你在這平復一下
while you regain your control.
沒事了
It's okay.
交給我  孩子
Hand it to me, girl.
她死了
She's dead!
杜克女士死了
Lady Trask is dead!
你干了什么
What did you do?
瑪麗叫我做的事啊
What Mary told me to do.
她讓你去恐嚇那女人  不是殺了她
She told you to frighten the woman, not slaughter her.
但是她罪有應得啊
But she deserved it.
我們厭倦了
We're tired.
厭倦了被暴打被利用
Tired of being beaten and used.
我們不要再被利用了
We won't be used anymore
任何一人
Any of us.
我們不會再忍氣吞聲
We won't take it.
讓開道  讓開道
Make way! Make way!
艾薩克
Isaac!
艾薩克  發生了什么
Isaac, what's happened?
杜克夫人死了  死得很慘
Mrs. Trask has been found dead -- horribly dead.
他們都認為是巴克一家干的
And they all think the Barkers are responsible.
經過那場爭執和小多莉看到的一切之后
After the fight and what little Dollie saw,
又發生這事  他們開始叫他們巫師了
now this, they're calling them witches.
奧登上尉在哪
Where is Captain Alden?
哪也找不到他
He is nowhere to be found.
大家等一等
People, wait!
等下  你們干什么
Wait! What are you doing?!
他們是被詛咒的巴克一家
Those damned Barkers!
他們詛咒了我們太多人
They've cursed too many of us.
他們干了什么
What have they done?!
我們過冬的糧食都腐爛了
Rotted all our winter supply of grain!
她殺了善良的杜克
She killed goody Trask!
證據呢  你們有任何證據嗎
Proof?! Have any of you any proof?!
讓開道  說你呢
Make way! You there!
整個鎮子都瘋了
The whole town has gone mad!
我們得阻止他們
We have got to stop them!
沒有什么比烏合之眾更可怕了
Nothing more dangerous than a mob.
最好別進行干涉
Best not to intervene.
你是地方法官  你代表著法律
You are magistrate. You represent the law.
沒有群眾支持  法律毫無意義
The law's meaningless without support of the people.
朋友們  鄰居們
Friends! Neighbors!
塞勒姆的人們  停手吧
People of Salem, stop!
想想你們要做的事
Think what you do!
你知道巫師存在
You know there are witches!
你告訴我們的
You've told us so!
而這里就是其中的三個
And here be three of them!
你要怎么處置他們
What will you do with them?!
如果他們是巫師  我們會辨明的
If they be witches, we will find out.
但這不是正確的方式
But this is not the way!
你就這么放過他們嗎
Would you just let them go?
不
No.
不  我們把他們關進監獄
No, we put them in the jail!
我們關他們一晚來平復心情
We hold them for the night while passions cool.
而當天空明亮之時
And then in the clear light of day,
我們將會在法律范圍內審判他們
we will examine them as the law allows!
我們之中每個人都有辯護的權利
Every one of us has the right to defend ourselves,
對我們的指責進行回應
to respond to our accusers!
杜克夫人死了  像羊羔一樣被殘殺
Mrs. Trask is dead, slaughtered like a lamb!
沒錯
True.
今夜不幸已經發生
Evil has been done this night already.
但是不要用更多的不幸來加重它
But do not compound it by doing more.
不要心急得去做無法挽回的事情
Do not rush to do what can never be undone.
如果他們現在有罪
If they be guilty now,
那么明早他們依然會有罪
they will be just as guilty in the morning.
但要通過公平的審判
After a fair trial.
說得沒錯
Quite right.
各位  把他們送進監獄
Men, take them to the jail.
巫師  殺人犯  殺人犯
Witches! Murderers! Murderers!
殺人犯
Murderers!
柯頓  我覺得這是我見過最英勇的行為
Cotton, I think that was the bravest thing I've ever seen.
就像是看一個男人把頭伸進獅子嘴
Like watching a man stick his head inside of a lion's jaws.
我會獎勵你的英勇的
I would reward you for your bravery.
我很愿意接受
I would gladly accept it,
但現在不是時候
but now is not the time.
我不能再否認我的感情了  它們是真實的
I cannot deny my feelings. They are real.
我不再滿足于只是你的顧客了
But I do not want any longer to be your customer.
你明白嗎
Do you understand?
我想是的
I think so.
我還會見到你嗎
Will I ever see you again?
當然
Yes.
但不是現在
But you must leave me now...
等我整理好一切
till I sort things out.
在那之后  一切都會不同
When I do, everything will be different.
我向你保證
I promise.
等等
Wait.
七年了  我已經等得夠久了
Seven years is a long enough time to wait.
停下
Stop.
瑪麗
Mary.
我知道你也夢見過這一切
I know you've dreamt of this.
面對夢境  你只能二選一
When it comes to dreams, you only got one choice.
徹底忘記
You forget them...
還是繼續活在夢境中
or you live them.
我已經不想再試著去遺忘了
And I'm done trying to forget them.
如果我們活在其中的
And what if in living our dreams
是一場噩夢呢
they become nightmares?
只要你我在一起就夠了
All that matters is you and me.
你總是將一切都說得很容易
You always make everything sound so simple.
你與西布里沒有子嗣
You don't have any children with Sibley.
你也不可能在乎他
You can't care about him.
由始至終
You haven't cared about
你也從不在乎旁人的想法  所以就這么一次
what other people have thought before, so for once...
讓我們為自己而活
...let's just live for us.
我真希望可以這么做
I wish it were possible.
為什么不行
And why isn't it?
就是不行
It just isn't.
請你離開
I want you to leave.
不
No.
我已經從你身上得到想要的一切了
I've gotten all I needed from you.
請你離開
Please leave.
你到底是怎么了
What happened to you?
有什么是你沒告訴我的
What are you not telling me?
這一切根本說不通
Because this makes no sense.
既然如此
Well...
很高興能為您效勞
...I'm happy to have been of service.
怎么了  哪里起火了
What is it?! What's burning?!
是巴克一家  他們都被當成巫師燒了
The Barkers! All of them burned as witches!
什么
What?!
誰下的命令
By whose authority?!
是我
Mine.
父親
Father.
我想我是對你那幼稚的好奇心
I see now I've indulged your juvenile curiosity
放縱過頭了
far, far too much.
看看你
Look at you.
被這些軟弱的理智道德工具所束縛
Surrounding yourself with all these feeble tools of reason.
但父親  他們可能是無辜的
But, father, they might have been innocent.
無辜
Innocent?
他們哪里無辜了
Innocent of what?
這一家人是出了名的流氓無賴
The family is well-known as wastrels and curs.
他們沒有經過審判  檢查
They had no trial, no examination.
他們將會在最偉大
And they shall receive their trial
最仁慈的法官面前接受審判
before the greatest and most merciful of judges.
如果他們真是無辜的
Indeed if they are deemed to be innocent,
我相信上帝會好好回報他們的
I trust the lord will see to their recompense.
但你
But you...
你的智商都去哪了
you -- have you turned imbecile?
你做的一切只是埋下了致命的懷疑之種
All you do is sow the deadly seeds of doubt.
難道你不知道
Do you not see,
當追捕巫師時
when hunting witches,
寧可殺死一百個無辜者
far better a hundred innocents die
也絕不能放過一個巫師
than a single solitary witch walks free?
知道嗎
Yes!
現在給我坐下
Now, sit you down.
好好想想你的過錯
Consider your mistakes.
坐下
Sit.
你要去哪
Where are you going?
這個時候也沒人能讓你燒了
There's no one left to burn at this hour.
注意言辭  孩子
Watch your tongue, boy.
難道你以為如今我就不敢拿鞭子抽你了嗎
You think you're too old to be whipped by your father, hmm?
你來遲了
You're too late.
我還以為你會來拯救我們
I thought you were going to save us.
但或許我們根本不值得被救
But maybe we just don't deserve saving.
我得承認  這是幅上佳的異教徒之作
It's a pretty piece of paganism, I'll grant you.
但恐怕不太適合公之于眾
But not fit for public viewing.
所以我將它掛在了臥室
That is why it enlightens my bedroom,
只有我至親至愛之人才能得見
where only my nearest and dearest are allowed.
比如你  親愛的英克里斯
Like you, my dear Increase.
你不知道見到你對我來說意味著什么
I can't tell you what it means to see you.
倫敦的皇家法庭如何
How was London and the King's Court?
一如既往地腐敗
Corrupt, as always.
國王批準了我們的新憲章
The king has granted us a new charter,
給予我們選擇之地的所有權力
full claim on this chosen land of ours,
他還答應春季便會給我們指派一位新的長官
and he promises a new governor in the spring,
一位精通戰術之人
a man experienced in warfare,
來助我們驅逐并根除那些異端匪徒
to help us purge and eradicate the heathen savages
永遠地斬除他們
in our midst for now and forever.
看來你真是不虛此行
What a tremendous victory for you.
對我們來說都是
For all of us.
確實
Indeed.
當我踏上歸途時  心中充滿了喜悅
When I set sail for home, I was full of elation.
仿佛僅憑希望便能載我回家
I could have sailed on my hopes alone.
我早該預料到那些邪惡力量
I should have known that the forces of evil
會前來阻撓我
would try to hinder me.
誰
Who?
法國人派來的奸細嗎
Agents of the French?
巫師
Witches.
當然了  他們竭盡全力
Of course, they did all they could.
靜止了海風  困住了帆船
They stilled the winds and trapped the ship.
四處傳播疾病與異議
They spread disease and dissent all around.
許多人死了
Many died.
但他們不會白白死去
But they did not die in vain.
感謝上帝你能平安歸來
Praise god you made it
為我們這個烏云籠罩的小鎮帶來一絲曙光
and landed safely on our shores to lighten our benighted town,
就像沉沉黑夜之后重現的耀眼太陽
like the sun returning after the darkest of nights.
瑪麗·西布里
Mary Sibley,
無論黑夜多深
However dark the night,
也遮掩不了你雙眸的光芒
your eyes still shine so brightly.
我依然堅信  就算保守病痛侵蝕
You know, I do believe my good friend George,
我的好友喬治仍然是塞勒姆最幸運的男人
for all his suffering, is the luckiest man in Salem.
這么說起來  我很想見見我這位好友
And speaking of my friend, I should like to see him.
可以嗎
May I?
他如今狀況很糟
He is particularly unwell.
好不容易  他現在終于睡著了
Thankfully, he's resting at present.
不如你明天再來
You must return tomorrow.
我相信你的到來一定會讓他無比開心的
I'm sure the very sight of you will cheer him immensely,
就像我一樣
As it has me.
您的到來對深陷黑暗的塞勒姆人民來說
Your presence in Salem can only be a tonic
真是一劑救命良藥
for all of us in these dark times.
不知此次您會在鎮上停留多久呢
How long may we enjoy your curative presence in town?
這個嘛
Why...
直到我見證那些惡魔的妓女
...until every last devil's whore of a witch
塞勒姆最后一個巫師死去
in Salem is dead.